Women Against War; Records apap391
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Yahoo Group Correspondence, 2002-2021
  - OWN-Iraq Health, 2005 January 11 - 2006 April 22
    - Speaker advice requested from WAW in Albany, NY, 2005 January 11
    - Meeting Minutes, 2005 January 13
    - No word yet from Code Pink, 2005 January 16
    - DU in Baghdad hospitals - just starting to see it in births, 2005 January 18
    - Meeting Notice WAW Iraq Public Health Committee - Wed. Jan. 26th, 2005 January 20
    - Re: Iraq Health Meeting Notice WAW Iraq Public Health Committee - Wed. Jan. 26th, 2005 January 20
    - DU proven present in 2003 in Iraqi civilians, 2005 January 21
    - Re: Public Health in Iraq, 2005 January 22
    - WAW Iraq Public Health Committee - Speaker possibilities, 2005 January 23
    - Re: Iraq Health WAW Iraq Public Health Committee - Speaker possibilities, 2005 January 25
    - Re: Iraq Health WAW Iraq Public Health Committee - Speaker possibilities, 2005 January 26
    - AMC Room, 2005 January 26
    - Meeting tonight cancelled!!, 2005 January 26
    - Re: Iraq Health AMC Room, 2005 January 26
    - Possible Speakers, 2005 January 26
    - Re: Iraq Health Possible Speakers, 2005 January 26
    - RE: Iraq Health WAW Iraq Public Health Committee - Speaker possibilities, 2005 January 27
    - RE: Iraq Health Possible Speakers, 2005 January 27
    - RE: Iraq Health Meeting tonight cancelled!!, 2005 January 27
    - films/documentaries, 2005 January 28
    - Potential speakers, 2005 January 29
    - Re: Iraq Health Potential speakers, 2005 January 30
    - DU Forum 2/18 at Channing Hall 7:30 pm, 2005 February 1
    - RE: Iraq Health DU Forum 2/18 at Channing Hall 7:30 pm, 2005 February 2
    - Re: Iraq Health Potential speakers, 2005 February 2
    - Attachments you can hopefully open!, 2005 February 2
    - Next Committee Meeting, 2005 February 5
    - FYI- Garfield is one of the author's of the Lancet report, 2005 February 5
    - More FYI from Voices in the Wilderness, 2005 February 5
    - re Cathy Breen, 2005 February 5
    - RE: Iraq Health Next Committee Meeting, 2005 February 6
    - Do you have any technical problems adding me to your listserv?, 2005 February 7
    - Emailing: 0,9171,1025139,00, 2005 February 7
    - RE: Iraq Health Do you have any technical problems adding me to your listserv?, 2005 February 7
    - Re: Iraq Health Next Committee Meeting, 2005 February 7
    - I snipped the segment on DU from Maureen's email. Good resource! Voices in the Wilderness, 2005 February 7
    - I am home due to inclement forecast, 2005 February 14
    - Important! Iraqi Public Health Planning Meeting, 2005 February 15
    - RE: Iraq Health Important! Iraqi Public Health Planning Meeting, 2005 February 15
    - FW: NOT IN OUR NAME!, 2005 February 15
    - You were invited by Barb Cooley to visit Occupation Watch!, 2005 February 16
    - Minutes of WAW Iraq Public Health Committee, 2005 February 16
    - Action step (2), 2005 February 16
    - Fwd: Dr. Sheri Fink, author of War Hospital; March 7; NOON; ME300, 2005 February 18
    - RE: Iraq Health Fwd: Dr. Sheri Fink, author of War Hospital; March 7; NOON; ME300, 2005 February 21
    - co-sponsorship?, 2005 February 26
    - Re: Iraq Health co-sponsorship?, 2005 February 27
    - SNOW, 2005 February 27
    - RE: Iraq Health SNOW, 2005 February 27
    - Re: Iraq Health co-sponsorship?, 2005 February 27
    - Re: Iraq Health co-sponsorship?, 2005 February 28
    - RE: Iraq Health SNOW, 2005 February 28
    - Meeting tonight, 2005 February 28
    - RE: Iraq Health Meeting tonight, 2005 February 28
    - Don't seem to be able to participate at a planning level for this program, 2005 February 28
    - I missed message #64 - hard bounce, 2005 March 2
    - Plan on Richard for the 28th, 2005 March 4
    - From Richard Garfield - Info Summary, 2005 March 4
    - iraq cv para- from Richard Garfield, 2005 March 4
    - Fw: [iac-discussion] U.S. used banned weapons in Fallujah - Health ministry, 2005 March 5
    - Take a look at Richard Garfield's summary, 2005 March 5
    - Richard's response as to his realationship to Lancet - so far!, 2005 March 5
    - Emailing: lancet9- note Garfield quote - I'mworried for nothing!, 2005 March 5
    - Note entire report is searhable - see left, 2005 March 5
    - Donations, 2005 March 5
    - Re: from cathy breen, 2005 March 6
    - Fw: from cathy breen, 2005 March 6
    - Kathy Kelly's response re my query re, 2005 March 7
    - Re: Iraq Health From Richard Garfield - Info Summary, 2005 March 7
    - Fw: from cathy breen- I told her we would wait until she decided ( tomorrow?) for sure, 2005 March 8
    - Re: Iraq Health Fw: from cathy breen- I told her we would wait until she deci..., 2005 March 8
    - RE: Iraq Health Fw: from cathy breen- I told her we would wait until she deci..., 2005 March 9
    - please excuse my off the top of the head ruminations, 2005 March 12
    - Here are my off the top of the head ruminations... excuse or not, as you wish, 2005 March 13
    - Iraq Co-Sponsorship Letter, 2005 March 13
    - RE: Iraq Health Iraq Co-Sponsorship Letter, 2005 March 13
    - FW: Re: march 9: Framing SS planning group meeting, 2005 March 13
    - RE: Iraq Health Iraq Co-Sponsorship Letter, 2005 March 14
    - Draft language for the policy petition, 2005 March 14
    - RE: Iraq Health Draft language for the policy petition, 2005 March 14
    - policy petition suggestion, 2005 March 15
    - Kerbala-EMERGENCY Updates - Please Read - but I will bring a couple of sets to share also, 2005 March 15
    - RE: Iraq Health Kerbala-EMERGENCY Updates - Please Read - but I will bring a couple of sets to share also, 2005 March 15
    - Fw: from cathy- it's a go!, 2005 March 16
    - Responses from Alberto Colombi re Donations to Emergency, 2005 March 16
    - Fw: EPIC's Latest Dispatch- Please read and consider, 2005 March 16
    - RE: Iraq Health Responses from Alberto Colombi re Donations to Emergency, 2005 March 17
    - Missed messages, 2005 March 17
    - Re: Iraq Health Responses from Alberto Colombi re Donations to Emergency, 2005 March 18
    - Re: Iraq Health Fw: EPIC's Latest Dispatch- Please read and consider, 2005 March 18
    - Iraq Public Health Meeting Minutes, 2005 March 18
    - Revised Petition, 2005 March 19
    - Re: Iraq Health Revised Petition, 2005 March 19
    - Iraq Health Revised Petition- a few suggestions in CAPS, 2005 March 20
    - Re: Iraq Health Revised Petition- a few suggestions in CAPS, 2005 March 21
    - RE: Iraq Health Revised Petition, 2005 March 21
    - Re: Iraq Health Revised Petition, 2005 March 22
    - FW: Re: Women Against War's Forum on Public Health in Iraq, 2005 March 22
    - Petition, 2005 March 22
    - Re: Iraq Health FW: Re: Women Against War's Forum on Public Health in Iraq, 2005 March 22
    - Re: Iraq Health Petition, 2005 March 22
    - Re: Iraq Health Iraq Public Health Meeting Minutes, 2005 March 23
    - Draft Petition, 2005 March 23
    - Re: Iraq Health FW: Re: Women Against War's Forum on Public Health in Iraq, 2005 March 23
    - Re: Iraq Health FW: Re: Women Against War's Forum on Public Health in Iraq, 2005 March 25
    - Re: Iraq Health Iraq Public Health Meeting Minutes, 2005 March 28
    - Public Health Petition - Draft, 2005 March 29
    - Minutes of March 28 Planning Mtg, 2005 March 29
    - Re: Iraq Health Public Health Petition - Draft, 2005 March 29
    - RE: Iraq Health Public Health Petition - Draft, 2005 March 30
    - what about trying to get, 2005 March 31
    - Re: Carol Bellamy, 2005 March 31
    - Iraq Health, about trying to get a new speaker....., 2005 March 31
    - trying to get a new speaker....., 2005 March 31
    - Sorry not to be responding, 2005 March 31
    - Re: Iraq Health Sorry not to be responding, 2005 April 1
    - Re: Iraq Health Re: Carol Bellamy, 2005 April 1
    - RE: Iraq Health trying to get a new speaker....., 2005 April 1
    - Fw: from cathy, 2005 April 1
    - regarding other speakers, 2005 April 1
    - Please review, 2005 April 1
    - Emailing: ContinuingCollateralDamage, 2005 April 1
    - FYI:I wish I had brought this info to our meeting the other night- note prominence of Sidel, 2005 April 1
    - Some names to add to our list - for future reference even!- from Kathy Kelly, 2005 April 1
    - Fw: [nysnet] Northeast P&J Action Conf- please share with all relevant contacts, 2005 April 1
    - RE: Iraq Health Please review, 2005 April 2
    - please share - more information to follow - this will be a really enjoyable stimulating evening out - check out Dave's web-site, 2005 April 2
    - I Did Receive a Phone Message ------, 2005 April 3
    - RE: Iraq Health I Did Receive a Phone Message ------, 2005 April 4
    - RE: Iraq Health Please review, 2005 April 4
    - RE: Iraq Health FYI:I wish I had brought this info to our meeting the other night- note prominence of Sidel, 2005 April 4
    - Advise and I will follow!- some suggestions from IPPNW, 2005 April 4
    - Regarding Richard Garfield, 2005 April 5
    - Re: Iraq Health Regarding Richard Garfield, 2005 April 5
    - RE: Iraq Health Regarding Richard Garfield, 2005 April 6
    - Fwd: Iraq Public Health Event, 2005 April 6
    - Input needed immediately - Public Health Speakers, 2005 April 6
    - Re: Iraq Health Input needed immediately - Public Health Speakers, 2005 April 6
    - BORDC Event, 2005 April 6
    - RE: Iraq Health Fwd: Iraq Public Health Event, 2005 April 6
    - I vote for 4/28 +focus on medical community, not peace groups, 2005 April 6
    - RE: Iraq Health BORDC Event, 2005 April 6
    - Re: Iraq Health BORDC Event, 2005 April 7
    - Re: Iraq Health Input needed immediately - Public Health Speakers, 2005 April 7
    - just saw this in Beth. Neighbors for Peace newsletter email, 2005 April 7
    - Postponement of April 28 Iraq Public Health Event, 2005 April 7
    - Next Iraq Public Health Planning Meeting, 2005 April 7
    - Re: Iraq Health Input needed immediately - Public Health Speakers, 2005 April 7
    - re Richard and May Date, 2005 April 7
    - Re: Iraq Health Input needed immediately - Public Health Speakers, 2005 April 8
    - forum pub. health, 2005 April 8
    - Re: [bethlehem_for_peace] Peacemail #138, 2005 April 9
    - The handout on past and present public health conditions in Iraq, 2005 April 10
    - Re: Iraq Health The handout on past and present public health conditions in Iraq, 2005 April 10
    - I will not be able to get to Albany for the meeting tonight, 2005 April 11
    - RE: Iraq Health forum pub. health, 2005 April 11
    - Minutes of April 11 Iraq Public Health Mtg, 2005 April 11
    - Dr. Carpenter, 2005 April 11
    - Other Social Justive Events May 16-24, 2005 April 11
    - Unifem Report on Iraq, 2005 April 11
    - RE: Iraq Health Other Social Justive Events May 16-24, 2005 April 12
    - RE: Iraq Health Unifem Report on Iraq, 2005 April 12
    - FW: Speaking possibility, 2005 April 14
    - Re: Iraq Health Unifem Report on Iraq, 2005 April 15
    - Re: Iraq Health Unifem Report on Iraq, 2005 April 16
    - please read, 2005 April 17
    - Re: Iraq Health please read, 2005 April 18
    - FW: Speaker on Iraq, 2005 April 19
    - Re: Iraq Health FW: Speaker on Iraq, 2005 April 19
    - My 2 cents Speaker on Iraq, 2005 April 19
    - do you want me, 2005 April 20
    - Re: Iraq Health My 2 cents Speaker on Iraq, 2005 April 20
    - might be a useful link!, 2005 April 20
    - Re: Iraq Health do you want me, 2005 April 20
    - SUNY school of Public Health, 2005 April 20
    - NUCLEAR PROLIFERATION: HOPE YOU CAN ATTEND THE TALK BY RANDALL FORSBERG AT SIENA - THURSDAY - 05/21 AT 7:30 PM- PLEASE POST AND SHARE, 2005 April 20
    - PLEASE NOTE FORSBERG TALK IS TONIGHT - NOT NEXT MONTH!!!!! NUCLEAR PROLIFERATION: HOPE YOU CAN ATTEND THE TALK BY RANDALL FORSBERG AT SIENA - THURSDAY - 04/21 AT 7:30 PM- PLEASE POST AND SHARE, 2005 April 21
    - Fw: Firsthand Report from Iraq - Wed 4/27, 2005 April 21
    - Re: Iraq Health do you want me, 2005 April 21
    - RE: Iraq Health Fw: Firsthand Report from Iraq - Wed 4/27, 2005 April 21
    - Shall we invite reps from med. comm. to join in planning?, 2005 April 21
    - Excellent report on Marla Ruzicka on yesterday's Democracy Now!, 2005 April 22
    - Staggering figures, 2005 April 22
    - Marla Ruzicka, 2005 April 22
    - a close up view health carein Iraq, 2005 April 22
    - This is a series of articles which you will find of value I suspect, 2005 April 22
    - Next Steps, 2005 April 25
    - Re: Iraq Health Next Steps, 2005 April 25
    - Re: Iraq Health Next Steps, 2005 April 26
    - A strategically planned outreach takes time?, 2005 April 26
    - RE: Iraq Health A strategically planned outreach takes time?, 2005 April 27
    - Re: Iraq Health Next Steps, 2005 April 27
    - Emailing: bad5cdd6e59942ed1a0bb28fa28163fa, 2005 April 27
    - Public Health, 2005 April 28
    - Re: Iraq Health Public Health, 2005 April 28
    - richard garfield response, 2005 April 29
    - RE: Iraq Health richard garfield response, 2005 April 29
    - re Garfiled, 2005 April 29
    - Fw: Emergency-USA NEW mail list/ invitation to subscribe, 2005 April 29
    - AN INVITATION YOU SHOULDN'T RESIST! THE WORLD'S ONLY SINGING CIA AGENT DESCENDS ON CAPITAL REGION- PLEASE SHARE THIS ANNOUNCEMENT WIDELY, 2005 April 29
    - Re: Iraq Health re Garfiled, 2005 April 29
    - Cathy Breen, 2005 April 29
    - handout, 2005 May 2
    - Re: Iraq Health handout, 2005 May 3
    - Back on Track, 2005 May 5
    - Re: Iraq Health Back on Track, 2005 May 5
    - RE: Iraq Health Back on Track, 2005 May 6
    - DU Testing Bill Rocks Through Louisiana House!, 2005 May 6
    - RE: Iraq Health DU Testing Bill Rocks Through Louisiana House!, 2005 May 6
    - Re: Iraq Health Back on Track, 2005 May 7
    - DU Munitions Action Plan - an Addendum, 2005 May 7
    - May 14 DU event in Saugerties, and more..., 2005 May 8
    - Richard Garfield, 2005 May 9
    - Re: Iraq Health Richard Garfield, 2005 May 9
    - Re: Iraq Health SUNY School of Public Health, 2005 May 10
    - Re: Iraq Health Richard Garfield, 2005 May 10
    - FW: AMC Room, 2005 May 10
    - DU and birth defects and cancers NOW in Iraq, 2005 May 10
    - DU Good news on CONN bill!, 2005 May 11
    - RE: Iraq Health DU and birth defects and cancers NOW in Iraq, 2005 May 11
    - Re: Iraq Health SUNY School of Public Health, 2005 May 11
    - Re: Iraq Health SUNY School of Public Health, 2005 May 12
    - Nov. 2004 article child malnutrition rates in Iraq, 2005 May 12
    - Jan. 2004 DU research - looks excellent, 2005 May 12
    - Re: Iraq Health SUNY School of Public Health, 2005 May 13
    - Richard Garfield, 2005 May 13
    - Re Date and Garfiled, 2005 May 13
    - The Iraqi health and infrastructure handout (at least the first version) is finally done!, 2005 May 13
    - Re: Iraq Health The Iraqi health and infrastructure handout (at least the first version) is finally done!, 2005 May 14
    - Richard Garfield, 2005 May 14
    - Please read the Canadian woman journalist's - Hadani Ditmar's - piece on Iraq - an interesting idea for a speaker, 2005 May 15
    - FW: Date, do we have one?, 2005 May 15
    - Re: Iraq Health FW: Date, do we have one?, 2005 May 15
    - RE: Iraq Health The Iraqi health and infrastructure handout (at least the first version) is finally done!, 2005 May 16
    - RE: Iraq Health Richard Garfield, 2005 May 16
    - US testing new weapons in Iraq, 2005 May 16
    - Re: Iraq Health Richard Garfield, 2005 May 17
    - Re: Iraq Health US testing new weapons in Iraq, 2005 May 17
    - Involving "The Health Show" in the event, 2005 May 17
    - Re: Iraq Health Involving "The Health Show" in the event, 2005 May 17
    - AMC Room Reservation, 2005 May 17
    - Re: Iraq Health AMC Room Reservation, 2005 May 18
    - Welcoming people to our event!, 2005 May 18
    - More about singing, 2005 May 18
    - Re: Iraq Health Welcoming people to our event!, 2005 May 19
    - RE: Iraq Health More about singing, 2005 May 19
    - Re: Iraq Health SUNY School of Public Health, 2005 May 19
    - Re: Iraq Health The Iraqi health and infrastructure handout (at least the first version) is finally done!, 2005 May 19
    - Re: Iraq Health Richard Garfield, 2005 May 19
    - Re: Iraq Health Welcoming people to our event!, 2005 May 19
    - Re: Iraq Health AMC Room Reservation, 2005 May 19
    - re Cathy Breen, 2005 May 19
    - re 06/09, 2005 May 19
    - June 9th Iraq Public Health, 2005 May 19
    - Re: Iraq Health AMC Room Reservation, 2005 May 19
    - Re: Iraq Health June 9th Iraq Public Health, 2005 May 19
    - Re: Iraq Health SUNY School of Public Health, 2005 May 20
    - Congratulations on finalizing a date for the Iraqi health presentation, 2005 May 20
    - RE: Iraq Health Congratulations on finalizing a date for the Iraqi health presentation, 2005 May 20
    - RE: Iraq Health Welcoming people to our event!, 2005 May 20
    - A side issue (but important), 2005 May 20
    - Forgot the flyer-oops!, 2005 May 20
    - RE: Iraq Health More about singing, 2005 May 20
    - RE: Iraq Health June 9th Iraq Public Health, 2005 May 20
    - things to do re: media outreach and music preparation, 2005 May 20
    - Re: Iraq Health AMC Room Reservation, 2005 May 20
    - Re: Iraq Health AMC Room Reservation, 2005 May 21
    - June 9th public health event, 2005 May 22
    - RE: Iraq Health June 9th public health event, 2005 May 22
    - JUNE 4 Conf. I am tabling for DU - could offer JUNE 9 flyers as well, 2005 May 22
    - Re: Iraq Health AMC Room Reservation, 2005 May 22
    - Major report on Iraq due out in a week, 2005 May 23
    - Paul Newmanfund takes kids to Jordan hospitals for care, 2005 May 23
    - 1700 CROSSES LAID IN FONDA; MEMORIAL SERVICE ON SUNDAY; PLEASE BROADCAST WIDELY, 2005 May 24
    - RE: Iraq Health things to do re: media outreach and music preparation, 2005 May 24
    - Re: Iraq Health AMC Room Reservation, 2005 May 24
    - Re: Iraq Health Congratulations on finalizing a date for the Iraqi health presentation, 2005 May 24
    - Re: Iraq Health June 9th Iraq Public Health, 2005 May 24
    - Two speakers lined Up, 2005 May 24
    - Re: Iraq Health Two speakers lined Up, 2005 May 24
    - Re: Iraq Health 1700 CROSSES LAID IN FONDA; MEMORIAL SERVICE ON SUNDAY; PLEASE BROADCAST WIDELY, 2005 May 25
    - Re: Iraq Health things to do re: media outreach and music preparation, 2005 May 25
    - Re: Iraq Health Two speakers lined Up, 2005 May 25
    - Flyer, 2005 May 25
    - Re: Iraq Health June 9th Iraq Public Health, 2005 May 25
    - Re: Iraq Health Flyer, 2005 May 26
    - June 4- Northeast Peace and Justice Activist Conference - Sage Colleges - Please Distribute Widely, 2005 May 26
    - RE: Iraq Health 1700 CROSSES LAID IN FONDA; MEMORIAL SERVICE ON SUNDAY; PLEASE BROADCAST WIDELY, 2005 May 26
    - Re: Iraq Health Two speakers lined Up, 2005 May 26
    - Re: Iraq Health Two speakers lined Up, 2005 May 27
    - Re: Iraq Names June 2nd WAW general meeting, 2005 May 28
    - Re: Iraq Health things to do re: media outreach and music preparation, 2005 May 28
    - music preparation for 6/9, 2005 May 28
    - RE: Iraq Health music preparation for 6/9, 2005 May 29
    - Emailing: antiwar, 2005 May 29
    - Legality of US fund reconstruction of health care system in Iraq, 2005 May 29
    - Gold StarFamilies for Peace, 2005 May 30
    - Fw: Music discussion continued..., 2005 May 30
    - Re: Iraq Health Fw: Music discussion continued..., 2005 May 30
    - NAKAO TAKATO and Fallujah etc. DVD, 2005 May 30
    - Re: Iraq Health Two speakers lined Up, 2005 May 30
    - Re: Iraq Health things to do re: media outreach and music preparation, 2005 May 30
    - Re: Iraq Health music preparation for 6/9, 2005 May 30
    - Do we have a room for Iraq Public health, 2005 May 30
    - To try and respond to a few different questions raised by your emails of this weekend, 2005 May 30
    - FYI Takato Nahoko, 2005 May 30
    - Pub health birth defects pix, 2005 May 30
    - Re: Iraq Health NAKAO TAKATO and Fallujah etc. DVD, 2005 May 30
    - fyi article what iraqi hospitals needed in feb 05, 2005 May 31
    - Legal issues under international law regarding pub.health in Iraq, 2005 May 31
    - update, 2005 May 31
    - Summary of Lancet Report and interview with Garfield, 2005 May 31
    - Emailing: Default, 2005 May 31
    - Ned McGlynn from Siena, 2005 May 31
    - Re AMC, 2005 May 31
    - DU resolutions in NYS counties! Interested?, 2005 May 31
    - Re: Iraq Health music preparation for 6/9, 2005 May 31
    - No Tracey?, 2005 June 1
    - Re: Iraq Health Summary of Lancet Report and interview with Garfield, 2005 June 1
    - Maureen's interview with Richard Garfield - another link, 2005 June 1
    - We are on - finally - on all counts!, 2005 June 1
    - AMC MC 100 - a place for us!, 2005 June 1
    - Re: Iraq Health No Tracey?, 2005 June 1
    - Re: Iraq Health We are on - finally - on all counts!, 2005 June 1
    - Flyer and Petition, 2005 June 1
    - Revised Public Health Flier, 2005 June 2
    - Re: Iraq Health To try and respond to a few different questions raised by your emails of this weekend, 2005 June 2
    - Re: Iraq Health We are on - finally - on all counts!, 2005 June 2
    - Re: Iraq Health Flyer and Petition, 2005 June 2
    - NO FLIERS ATTACHED are usable!!!!!!!! and MODERATOR, 2005 June 2
    - Re: Iraq Health Revised Public Health Flier, 2005 June 2
    - Public Health Flyer, 2005 June 2
    - Re: Iraq Health Public Health Flyer, 2005 June 2
    - items for discussion, 2005 June 2
    - JUNE 9 Public Health in Iraq Forum at Albany Med, 2005 June 2
    - Here's the final revision of the Iraq Health Consequences handout, 2005 June 2
    - Steve Breyman is going to record Richard Garfield's talk!, 2005 June 2
    - Re: Iraq Health NO FLIERS ATTACHED are usable!!!!!!!! and MODERATOR, 2005 June 2
    - Re: Iraq Health items for discussion, 2005 June 2
    - Re: Iraq Health Steve Breyman is going to record Richard Garfield's talk!, 2005 June 2
    - Re: Iraq Health We are on - finally - on all counts!, 2005 June 2
    - Public Health Task List, 2005 June 2
    - Re: Iraq Health We are on - finally - on all counts!, 2005 June 3
    - Re interview with Garfield, 2005 June 3
    - Re: Iraq Health Re interview with Garfield, 2005 June 4
    - Giveaway's of free tickets to the Clearwater Festival and Falcon Ridge Festivals, on WRPI, Sunday, June 5th, 4 PM through 8 PM, 2005 June 4
    - Re: Iraq Health Re interview with Garfield, 2005 June 5
    - RE: Iraq Health We are on - finally - on all counts!, 2005 June 6
    - Janice please forgive my uncertainty, 2005 June 7
    - Fw: Iraq Dispatches: Desperate for Work, Blind to Dangers, 2005 June 7
    - RE: Iraq Health Janice please forgive my uncertainty, 2005 June 7
    - The nearest parking for Thursday night, 2005 June 7
    - Re: The nearest parking for Thursday night, 2005 June 7
    - Please note Room correction as well as directions for Thursday's Forum, 2005 June 8
    - Re: Iraq Health Re: The nearest parking for Thursday night, 2005 June 8
    - Parking Guide, 2005 June 8
    - reminder, 2005 June 8
    - DU flyer - effect on Iraqi civilians JUNE 2005 update, 2005 June 8
    - Richard Garfield's interview with Steve Breyman, 11:00 am this morning, 2005 June 8
    - tabling, 2005 June 8
    - Re: Iraq Health tabling, 2005 June 8
    - RE: Iraq Health tabling, 2005 June 9
    - Thank you to all of the wonderful women who made the Iraq Public Health Forum possible, 2005 June 10
    - RE: Iraq Health Thank you to all of the wonderful women who made the Iraq Public Health Forum possible, 2005 June 10
    - RE: Iraq Health Thank you to all of the wonderful women who made the Iraq Public Health Forum possible, 2005 June 11
    - my reactions, 2005 June 12